toostep.com 2012-03-26

# 

**_Privacy Policy_**

We at TooStep know that you care how information about you is used and shared; we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. TooStep is an exclusive network of executives for their career enhancement. We combine knowledge sharing, referrals, jobs and professional networking channels effectively for your career enhancement and also create a high Return on Investment for strategic hiring need of corporates. Toostep uses various channels like Toostep.com Knowledge exchange network , Toostep JobSites and Toostep applications on social networks to provide these services . When you register with us, you provide personally identifiable information. Your privacy is our top concern. Please go through the details provided below to learn more about how you are identifiable and how your information is used and with whom it is shared and so on.

  1. **Information Collection**

1\. In order to become a TooStep user, you have to register using any of TooStep online channels and create a profile.

2\. Once a user, you may provide additional information in the Profile section describing your skills, professional experiences, and networking objectives. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration enables you to better identify yourself and find new opportunities in the TooStep system. The same shall also be used to customize your experience on TooStep. For example, when you login to your account we will display the screen names of new users who have recently joined your network.

3\. In order to invite others to connect with you directly in TooStep, you can either enter their email addresses or send requests on Social Networks. This information will be used by TooStep to send your invitation and reminders. You may also choose to Import contacts from your other email providers or networking communities. All information which is imported will only be viewable by you and will not be searchable by others in the TooStep network.

4\. All information that you enter or import about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as it covers your own personally identifiable information.

  2. **Cookies & Log Files**

Like most web sites, TooStep uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows TooStep to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use TooStep. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.

One type of cookie, known as a "persistent" cookie, is set once you have logged in to your TooStep account. The next time you visit the TooStep web site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user so you will not need to log in before using the service. Additionally, if you log out of the TooStep site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a "session" cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the TooStep site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the TooStep web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave TooStep. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the TooStep service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

  3. **Information Sharing**

    1. _Information Use_ **:**

### TooStep is an online service dedicated to help executives in effectively connecting with one another. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself to other users. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by TooStep Corporation from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by TooStep. This information can be utilized by TooStep in such manner as TooStep, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate

    2. **_Sharing Information with Third Parties_ :**

TooStep takes the privacy of our users very seriously. 

      1. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third party for marketing purposes. 
      2. We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. 
      3. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

TooStep offers a "public profile" feature which allows users to publish portions of their TooStep profile, including your "name", but not your "email address" to the public Internet. Users may opt-out of this feature; however TooStep does not warrant how third-parties search engines will update their cache.

We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by role (i.e. product managers, vice presidents), industry, geographic location, company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users activities on the site, please email customer service at [customerservice@toostep.com](mailto:customerservice@toostep.com).

We will transfer information about you if TooStep is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, TooStep will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the TooStep web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

    3. **_Communications between Users_ :**

Many emails you initiate through TooStep, an invitation sent to a non-user for instance, will list your email address and name in the header of the message. Emails you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network (for instance how many people are in your network), but will never list the people to whom you are directly connected. Other communications that you initiate through the TooStep, like a request for contact, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another user if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other.

  4. **_Legal Disclaimer_ :**

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

  4. **Outside Links**

TooStep may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by TooStep.

  5. **TooStep Communications**

TooStep will communicate with you through email and notices posted on its online channels. These include a series of welcome emails which help inform new users about various features of the service. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from TooStep related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user in your network sends you an opportunity. TooStep may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to [customerservice@toostep.com](mailto:customerservice@toostep.com).

  6. **Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your TooStep account, at any time by logging in to your account on TooStep and editing the information on your Profile page. You can also close your account through the TooStep . If you close your TooStep account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the TooStep Privacy Policy that you have previously agreed to. To close your account and remove your information from the TooStep service, please send your request to [customerservice@toostep.com](mailto:customerservice@toostep.com). Please send your request using the email account that you have registered with TooStep under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to [customerservice@toostep.com](mailto:customerservice@toostep.com) within three business days of our receiving it.

  7. **Security**

In order to secure your personal information, access to your data on TooStep requires logging in. To protect any data you store on our servers we also regularly audit our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and we use a tier-one secured-access data center.

  8. **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

TooStep may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. Notice of all changes that materially affects the way in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our privacy policy. If you continue to use the toostep service after notice of changes has been sent or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

  9. **Questions or Comments**

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please contact [customerservice@toostep.com](mailto:customerservice@toostep.com)
